Is there anyone here?
どなたかいらっしゃいますか？
Help!
助けてくれ！
Anyone’s here?
誰かいる？
I need help.
助けが必要なんだ。
Can anybody hear me?
誰か聞こえる？
Help me please!
助けてください！
You...
君は...
I’m dreaming like this again?
またこんな夢を見ているのか？
Are you up? Nu-lin.
起きてる？ヌーリン
Yes, I already woke up.
そう、もう目が覚めたんだ。
Today is the first day of your internship.
今日はインターンシップの初日だ。
Fighting
ファイティング
You should hurry and go shower.
急いでシャワーを浴びてきなさい。
Thanks, P’Sun.
ありがとう、プサン。
The total turnover of the Soul High Jewelry
ソウル・ハイ・ジュエリーの総売上高
doesn’t look really good for the past few quarters.
ここ数四半期はあまり良い印象がない。
We just started doing online business
オンラインビジネスを始めたばかり
so in the last quarter we spent a lot of money to invest there.
だから前四半期には、そこに投資するために大金を費やした。
No matter how much investment we put in
どれだけ投資をしても
it won’t do much if our designs are still outdated.
私たちのデザインが時代遅れのままでは、あまり意味がない。
Erm…
あの...
Mr. Somchai, Have a look at our new campaign please.
ソムチャイさん、我々の新しいキャンペーンを見てください。
I think it’s a bit too late.
ちょっと遅すぎると思う。
Or maybe our presenter may be able to attract
あるいは、私たちのプレゼンターが、そのような人たちを惹きつけることができるかもしれない。
enough buyers to make our brand become the attention of the market.
私たちのブランドを市場の注目の的とするのに十分なバイヤーがいる。
Are you implying
と言いたいのか？
that there are errors
エラーがあること
in our policy?
我々の政策に？
And also
そしてまた
Madame Wang is the one who handpicked the presenter herself.
マダム・ワンはプレゼンターを自ら選んだ人物だ。
But wasn't it because the vision
しかし、それはビジョンが
that we’ve been sworn by for the last 30 years
この30年間、私たちが誓ってきたこと。
made us successful?
私たちを成功に導いたのは？
It’s just
それはただ
at the moment….
今のところ......。
Huhh
フフフ
I’m sitting right here
私はここに座っている
just be honest about it.
正直に言えばいい。
What seems to be  the problem
何が問題なのか
just tell me directly.
直接言ってくれ
I’m going to be honest then
正直に言おう。
I think our vision
私たちのビジョンは
is very old fashioned.
はとても古い。
I think
私は思う。
that it’s time that we should consider rebranding.
そろそろリブランディングを検討すべき時期だと思う。
Soul High Jewelry really needs a change.
ソウル・ハイ・ジュエリーは本当に変化が必要だ。
Mr. Suriyen
スリエン氏
someone’s calling you.
誰かから電話だ。
Yes, mommy
はい、ママ
Alright
よし
Chan
チャン
Can you please get the car ready?
車の準備をお願いできますか？
We will be heading back to Bangkok.
これからバンコクに戻る。
Yes, sir.
はい
Please get in.
どうぞお入りください。
Thank you so much.
本当にありがとう。
Please drive safe.
安全運転をお願いします。
I’ve already arrived at the office.
もうオフィスに着いたよ。
I hope you have a good day.
良い一日をお過ごしください。
No matter what happened,
何が起きてもだ、
you can do it
君ならできる
Lin.
リン
Pim and Yo still haven’t arrived yet.
ピムとヨウはまだ到着していない。
Hello, Lin.
やあ、リン。
Hello, Pim where are you now?
こんにちは、ピム。
Still haven't got here?
まだ来ないのか？
No, I just got here
いや、ここに来たばかりなんだ
I’m going up there soon.
もうすぐそこに行くんだ。
Wait
待つ
and hold the door for me please!
ドアを開けておいてください
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Pim, wait for me too.
ピム、僕も待ってて。
Yo!
ヨー！
Pim, just wait for me a bit.
ピム、ちょっと待ってて。
The elevator is going up now.
今、エレベーターが上がっている。
Hurry!
急げ！
Faster!
もっと速く！
Come on!
さあ、行こう！
Yo!
ヨー！
Hurry!
急げ！
Please wait for my friend just a little moment.
私の友人を少々お待ちください。
Hey, two of you
お二人さん
want to come in or not?
入りたいのか、入りたくないのか？
We’re coming in.
今から行く
We are getting late now.
もう遅くなってしまった。
I’m sorry. Sorry.
ごめんなさい。ごめんなさい。
Hey!
やあ！
Wait!
待ってくれ！
I got here first.
私が先に着いた。
Sorry about that,
申し訳ない、
but I’m also in a hurry.
でも、急いでいるんだ。
Let’s go and close the doors too.
ドアも閉めに行こう。
Yo,
ヨー、
then I’m going up first. You need to hurry now!
じゃあ、僕が先に行くよ。今すぐ急ぐんだ
Pim!
ピム
Where is Yo?
ヨウはどこにいる？
I think he is on his way up here.
彼はここに来る途中だと思う。
What?
え？
Why isn’t he here yet?
なぜまだ来ないんだ？
Huhh
フフフ
Yo!
ヨー！
Finally, you’re here.
やっと来たね。
Hurry!
急げ！
เห้อ
เห้อ
I don’t know who that guy is
あいつが誰だか知らない
but he stole my spot on the elavator.
しかし、彼はエラベーターで私のポジションを奪った。
Yeah.
そうだね。
Hey!
やあ！
Nerdy,
オタクだ、
why did you steal my spot?
なぜ私のポジションを奪った？
I actually got there before you
実は私の方が先に着いた
and you also bumped into me as well.
あなたも私にぶつかった。
No! I got to the elevator first
いや、僕が先にエレベーターに乗ったんだ
and you are the one who bumped into me.
私にぶつかったのはあなたでしょう？
No, you bumped into me
いや、ぶつかった
I got to the elevato way ahead of you.
私はあなたよりずっと先にエレバトに着いた。
I was there first!
私が最初にそこにいた！
You bumped me!
私にぶつかった！
No, you bumped me!
いや、ぶつけられた！
No, it’s you!
いや、君だよ！
Quiet!
静かだ！
You guys
君たち
are already
すでに
10 minutes late
10分遅刻
on your first day!
初日に！
Here’ a thing,
こういうことだ、
the elevator was full
エレベーターは満員だった
and
そして
the was ‘something’
は「何か」だった
that stole my spot.
私のポジションを奪った
That is not an excuse
それは言い訳ではない
to be late.
遅刻する
Late is late. Doesn’t really matter.
遅刻は遅刻。そんなことはどうでもいい。
Go!
行くんだ！
And get back in the line with your friends.
そして友人たちと列に戻る。
Hey!
やあ！
You guys know
君たちは知っている
that being 10 minutes late
10分遅れたこと
might be nothing
何でもない
for you guys.
君たちのために。
But in the 10 minutes
しかし、10分の間に
can be super beneficial
非常に有益である
for us here at work.
私たちのために。
Hm?
ん？
If even just one of you were late
一人でも遅れたら
that meant that all of you were late as well.
ということは、君たちも遅刻したことになる。
As it is said that
と言われているように
one rotten apple
腐ったリンゴ一個
Ahem
エヘン
spoils the whole barrel.
樽全体を台無しにする。
Since here
ここから
we work as a team.
私たちはチームとして働く。
If you can’t even be on time,
時間さえ守れないなら、
how can you be responsible for anything?
どう責任を取るんだ？
Isn’t that right?
そうだろう？
Answer me. Isn't that right!
答えてくれ。そうだろう？
That’s right!
その通りだ！
Hands on your friends' necks.
友達の首に手を回す。
What!
何が？
I thought that we escaped
私たちは脱出したと思っていた
the SOTUS system.
SOTUSシステム
Come on,
さあ、行こう、
didn’t you say before that
以前、あなたはこう言わなかったか？
“where there's a will, there's a way”.
「意志あるところに道は開ける」。
What are you two whispering about!
二人とも何をひそひそ話しているんだ！
Repeat my command!
私の命令を繰り返せ！
Sqaut 10 times!
Sqautを10回！
Squat 10 times!
スクワット10回！
Start!
スタート！
Just what are you all doing now?
皆さんは今何をしているのですか？
Erm..
あの...
Er..
えー
P’Kaew, good morning.
プケウ、おはよう。
Well,
まあね、
I’m about to
これから
punish these interns
実習生を罰する
for being late.
遅刻したからだ。
I've been waiting for my interns for quite a while now.
インターンをずっと待っていたんだ。
Are all of these
これらはすべて
will be working in the design department right?
はデザイン部門で働くんだろう？
Er..
えー
They will be divided into 3 teams.
彼らは3つのチームに分かれる。
There are team A, B, and C.
チームA、B、Cがある。
พี่ พี่แก้วครับ
พี่แก้วครับ
Can I see
見せてくれる？
each team?
各チーム？
Er..
えー
Yes,
そうだ、
Team C!
チームC！
Where is team C?
Cチームは？
Okay,
オーケー、
team C you need to
チームC
follow Jen here.
ジェンをフォローする
You can go now.
もう行っていいよ。
Go. Go.
行け行け。
And what’s next?
次はどうする？
Where’s Team B?
チームBは？
You three need
あなた方3人に必要なのは
to
への
follow Mrs. Bow this way
ボウ夫人の後を追う
please.
お願いします。
P’ Kaew,
P' Kaew、
this is team A right?
これはチームAだよね？
Yes.
そうだ。
Team A,
チームA、
then
では
follows me
付いてくる
to the design department now.
今すぐデザイン部門へ
Work hard everybody!
みんな頑張ってくれ！
You’re in Team A?
チームAですか？
Yes, just go first.
そうだ、先に行けばいいんだ。
The building is quite far away.
建物はかなり遠い。
Fighting!
戦っている！
Dis, you need to come too!
ディス、君も来るんだ！
This is our design department building kiddos.
これは我々のデザイン部門が子供たちを作っているところだ。
It is a building that is separated from the executive building.
エグゼクティブ・ビルとは別の建物である。
Our company’s president or Madame Wang
社長の王です
really prioritizes our department.
私たちの部門を本当に優先している。
That’s why she wanted
だから彼女は
us to be surrounded by nature as much as she could.
できるだけ自然に囲まれていたいと思っていた。
That is so beautiful.
とても美しい。
Let’s go inside.
中に入ろう。
Stunning!
見事だ！
Sick!
病気だ！
During luch break
ルチ休憩中
if anyone wants to eat
食べたい人がいれば
there’s a room for it as well.
そのための部屋もある。
That room is located on the first floor where you were,
その部屋は、あなたがいた1階にあります、
there will be beverage
飲み物があります
and food provided for free
食事は無料
which is one of our policies as well.
これも我々のポリシーのひとつだ。
Wow!
ワオ！
This is my
これは私の
dream work place.
夢の職場。
I’m going to eat everything
何でも食べる
and even bring some home too.
そして、家に持って帰ることもできる。
Hurry and get inside.
急いで中に入って。
Hurry! Hurry!
急げ急げ
It’s really hot out here.
ここは本当に暑いんだ。
Here is our designing room.
ここが私たちの設計室だ。
We’ve been walking together for a while but I haven’t introduced myself yet.
しばらく一緒に歩いているけど、まだ自己紹介していないんだ。
My name is Kaewmanee.
私の名前はカエウマニー。
I am the head of the design department here.
私はここのデザイン部門の責任者だ。
Hello.
こんにちは。
My name is Salin.
私の名前はサリン。
I’m Pim.
ピムです。
My name is Yotha.
私の名前はヨタ。
And I’m Sam.
僕はサムだ。
Our department we work like a family,
私たちの部署は家族のように働いている、
so if you need my help
私の助けが必要なら
like what just happened
今起こったことのように
you  can tell me right away.
すぐに言ってくれ
And also
そしてまた
the rules of the interns who work here
ここで働くインターンのルール
aren’t really fussy.
はあまりうるさくない。
As for the uniform,
ユニフォームに関しては、
if it is an important
重要なことであれば
or the day that we might have a meeting.
あるいはミーティングがある日だ。
You must wear something formal
フォーマルな服装であること
like student uniforms.
学生服のように。
If it is a chill day
寒い日なら
at work
仕事中
you can dress appropriately.
適切な服装ができる。
It just needs to be a pair of  long pants and shoes that cover your heels.
長ズボンとかかとが隠れる靴があればいい。
Do not forget the name tag.
名札をお忘れなく。
It is really important in our company.
それは私たちの会社にとって本当に重要なことだ。
We must wear it all the time
常に身に着けていなければならない
when we are working here.
ここで仕事をしているとき
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Prim,
プリム
you got here just in time.
間に合ったね。
Why don’t you come and introduce yourself to our new interns.
新しいインターンたちに自己紹介をしに来てはどうだろう。
She’s our deputy head.
彼女は副ヘッドだ。
Her name is Primrada.
彼女の名前はプリムラーダ。
Hello
こんにちは
Please take care of us.
私たちをよろしくお願いします
Have you received the work that I sent to you?
私が送った作品は届いていますか？
Yes, I already got it.
はい、もう手に入れました。
Did you already print it out?
もうプリントアウトした？
Yes, I did.
ええ、そうです。
We need to have another meeting about this.
この件に関して、もう一度会議を開く必要がある。
Why is P’Prim so arrogant?
P'プリムはなぜそんなに傲慢なのか？
Yo!
ヨー！
She’s just cool
彼女はクールだ
not arrogant.
傲慢ではない。
Ah
ああ
So this is the one?
これがそうなのか？
Your idol who won
優勝したあなたのアイドル
the designing competition.
デザイン・コンペティション
when she was in university.
大学時代。
You were really into her right?
本当に彼女に夢中だったんだろう？
I’m going to pinch you just now!
私は今、あなたをつまむつもりだ！
Everybody,
みんなだ、
please take care of these interns.
実習生たちをよろしくお願いします。
I have a meeting with Prim
プリムと打ち合わせがある
so I need to go now.
だから、もう行かなければならない。
See you around!
また会おう！
This way please.
こちらへどうぞ
Oh
ああ
I forgot to tell you one thing.
ひとつ言い忘れた。
The document room
資料室
at the end of the hallway.
廊下の端にある。
It stores really important documents.
本当に重要な書類を保管している。
Please, try not to go in there
お願いだから、そこには行かないでくれ
if not necessary.
必要なければ。
Yes!
そうだ！
Let’s go.
行こう。
Hey!
やあ！
Insane?
非常識？
Alright!
わかったよ！
Are you guys ready to help me with all the work?
君たち、僕の仕事を手伝ってくれるかい？
So!
だから
Ready?
準備はいいか？
Yes!
そうだ！
Huh
はぁ
Seriously!
真面目な話だ！
Are we working in a designing company
我々はデザイン会社で働いているのか？
Or in a hotel?
それともホテルで？
Lin!
リン
It is going to spill.
こぼれそうだ。
Oh my god!
なんてことだ！
Sun, can you open the door?
サン、ドアを開けてくれる？
Come in. Come in.
どうぞお入りください。
Food is here.
食べ物はここにある。
Right here.
ここだよ。
Yo, hurry up!
ヨ、急げ！
Ugh!
うっ
Why do we have to carry these things in the middle of the night!
なぜ夜中にこんなものを運ばなければならないのか！
What else can we do?
他に何ができる？
This is what we got asked to do. Hurry, Yo!
これが依頼されたことだ。急げ、ヨー！
Wait.
待ってくれ。
Faster!
もっと速く！
Pff
プッ
If I own the company.
もし私が会社のオーナーならね。
I’m going to fire all of you.
私はあなたたち全員を解雇するつもりだ。
Don’t complain too much.
あまり文句を言うな。
Ouch!
痛い！
Yo
ヨー
What!
何が？
Darn it!
畜生！
Quick! Quick! Quick!
クイック急げ急げ
Yo, you have to be careful.
気をつけないといけないよ。
I know.
分かっている。
For real!
本当だよ！
Not yet, it is not clean yet.
まだだ。
It is a big cleaning day.
大掃除の日だ。
I should take a picture and report to the boss.
写真を撮ってボスに報告しなければ。
That’s why it is called a big cleaning day.
だから大掃除の日というわけだ。
Yes!
そうだ！
Yo,
ヨー、
did we really spend a hundred grand to work here?
ここで働くのに10万ドルも使っただろうか？
to work here?
ここで働くために？
I thought we are going to learn
私たちはこれから学ぶのだと思った
about jewelry.
ジュエリーについて
Turnt out we are currently cleaning the mirrors.
今、ミラーを掃除しているところなんだ。
Argh,
アーッ、
what’s wrong with you, Yo ?
どうしたんだ、ヨー？
I’m here as an intern in designing
私はインターンとしてデザインに携わっています。
not a a servnant.
使用人ではない。
They make me do so much.
彼らは私に多くのことをさせてくれる。
Your’re right!
その通りだ！
Lower your voice. They might hear you.
声を小さく。彼らに聞こえるかもしれない。
It’s hard enough as it is
今のままで十分難しい
or you want more chores from them.
あるいは、もっと家事をさせたいのか。
I’m so sick of it, Lin.
もううんざりだよ、リン。
Sick of what?
何の病気？
You didn't get to wipe the mirror
あなたは鏡を拭くことができなかった
and also didn’t carry boxes like us.
しかも、私たちのように箱を持っていなかった。
Can’t I be sick of those chores with you?
一緒に家事をするのは嫌にならない？
Fine.
素晴らしい。
Ops!
作戦だ！
Soul High Jewelry,
ソウル・ハイ・ジュエリー
Madame Wang who’s leading in Jewelry.
ジュエリーをリードするマダム・ワン。
Why did she offer jobs for these people?
なぜ彼女はこの人たちに仕事を提供したのか？
I don't get it.
私には理解できない。
I really wanna know,
本当に知りたいんだ、
if she doesn’t have any heir to run a company.
もし彼女に会社を経営する後継者がいなければ。
Maybe her son is also an incompetent.
息子も無能なのかもしれない。
What’s your problem?
何が問題なんだ？
No!
いや！
Got something in your throat!
のどに何か詰まっている
Don’t forget to have a meal.
食事も忘れずに。
Hey,
やあ、
What are you doing?
何をしているんだ？
What?
え？
Don’t forget to have a meal,
食事も忘れずに、
Lin.
リン
Hahaha
ハハハ
Stop it!
やめてくれ！
It’s because of two of you
ふたりのおかげだ
I have to talk with him.
彼と話をしなければならない。
If this is a movie,
これが映画ならね、
there should be a flashback scene.
フラッシュバックのシーンがあるはずだ。
One
ひとつ
Two
ふたつ
Three
スリー
Hi, friends.
やあ、友よ。
Meet my new boyfriend.
私の新しいボーイフレンドを紹介します。
Okay?
いいかい？
Finally,
最後に
we three get to intern in the same company.
私たち3人は同じ会社でインターンをすることになりました。
What are we waiting for then?
じゃあ、何を待っているんだ？
Cheer!
応援する！
Whoa!
おっと！
Ugh!
うっ
Yo againn.
ヨーアゲン。
Me again?
また私？
I can’t take it any more.
もう我慢できない。
Truth
真実
or Dare
またはダレ
Dare
あえて
I want my friend to have a relationship.
私は友人に交際を望んでいる。
Can you try
試してくれる？
using a dating app
出会い系アプリ
and
そして
talk with someone?
誰かと話す？
No!
いや！
I already told you that I don’t want to do that.
そんなことはしたくないとすでに言ったはずだ。
โอ๊ย
โอ๊ย
Lin,
リン
Huh?
え？
Let me take your pictures.
写真を撮らせてください。
Smile more.
もっと笑って。
Last one.
最後だ。
You’re cheating.
ズルをしている。
Did you really use his phone to download a dating app?
本当に彼の携帯を使って出会い系アプリをダウンロードしたのか？
Well, you did not specify who.
誰とは言っていない。
Isn’t ture?
そうだろう？
Yo’re so smart.
君はとても賢い。
This is why
これがその理由だ。
we are friends.
私たちは友人だ。
Pim,
ピム
is he hand some?
手もあるのか？
Very much so!
とてもそうだ！
Swipe right!
右にスワイプ！
Yeah!
そうだね！
Hello,
こんにちは、
my name is Sun.
私の名前は太陽です。
Who’s this?
これは誰だ？
Can you get the app and talk to someone?
アプリを入手して、誰かと話すことはできますか？
Lin, let me take your pictures.
リン、写真を撮らせてくれ。
Last one!
最後だ！
Swipe right!
右にスワイプ！
Yo!!!
ヨー！
Yay!
イェーイ！
Is it that funny?
そんなに面白いか？
You two keep mocking me.
君たちは私を馬鹿にしている。
Come on,
さあ、行こう、
at least what I did
少なくとも私は
got you someone to talk to.
話し相手ができた。
Your’re right.
その通りだ。
Where else can you find good friends like us?
私たちのようなよき友が他にどこにいる？
True!
その通りだ！
I mean
つまり
you’ve been talking with him for a while.
しばらく彼と話していたんだろう？
Have you met him in person yet?
もう彼に直接会った？
Oh my god!
なんてことだ！
Why?
なぜですか？
It’s been weeks
ここ数週間
and you haven’t even got to meet him.
あなたはまだ彼に会っていない。
Uhm,
うーん、
it’s that bad?
そんなに悪いのか？
Honestly,
正直なところだ、
I’m afraid
心配だ
so I think
そう
just only talk like this
このように話すだけでいい
is fine.
は大丈夫だ。
Or,
あるいは
are you scared of losing you v…
を失うことを恐れているのか？
Pim!
ピム
Hey,
やあ、
what are you thinking about?
何を考えているんだい？
You’re crazy!
どうかしている！
That’s right.
その通りだ。
I think
私は思う。
if you get a chance you should
機会があれば、ぜひ
go out with him.
彼と付き合う
Do you have any
あなたは何か持っていますか？
picture of him for me to see?
彼の写真を見せようか？
Hey!
やあ！
Go easy!
気楽に行こう！
We are just getting to know each other.
まだお互いを知り始めたばかりだ。
Why would you wanna know?
なぜ知りたいの？
Are you two close?
お二人は親しいのですか？
Yo..
ヨー...
Sam is also our friend.
サムは私たちの友人でもある。
Just be nice to each other.
ただ、お互いに親切にするんだ。
เออ
เออ
From the pictue,
写真より
I think
私は思う。
he’s around 30 years old.
彼は30歳前後だ。
In that picture,
その写真の中だ、
he also looks
彼はまた
like he’s in good shape
調子良さそう
and knows how to dress.
着こなしも心得ている。
A little bit like a bad boy maybe,
ちょっと不良少年みたいかもしれない、
wise, and
賢明で
gentle at the same time.
同時に優しい。
Those are kinda what he looks like.
それが彼の姿のようなものだ。
I can see the picture in my head.
頭の中に絵が浮かぶ。
Have a look, Sam.
見てごらん、サム。
His picture.
彼の写真
Why?
なぜですか？
Is he not okay?
大丈夫ですか？
Er..
えー
No, Lin.
いや、リン。
He looks good,
彼は元気そうだ、
but I agree with you
しかし、私はあなたに同意する
that you should talk a little longer before
その前に、もう少し話した方がいい
meeting him.
彼に会った。
People these days are not that good.
最近の人はそんなにいい人じゃない。
Just trust me.
ただ、私を信じてほしい。
Okay.
オーケー。
Are you okay?
大丈夫ですか？
Weren’t you just telling him to meet the guy?
あの男に会えと言ったんじゃないのか？
Just suddenly changed your mind.
急に気が変わっただけだ。
Do you not tell us anything?
何も話さないのか？
Why are you so concerned about me?
なぜ私のことをそんなに心配してくれるのですか？
Have a look yourself.
自分で見てみよう。
See?
分かるかい？
Let me see.
見せてくれ。
How is he?
彼はどうですか？
Got a pass?
パスは？
He looks good
彼は元気そうだ
but I look better.
でも、良くなった。
We should just hurry and eat
急いで食べよう
because we have to get back to work soon.
すぐに仕事に戻らなければならないからだ。
Argh!
アーッ！
Joykiller!
ジョイキラー
Why would you have to bring that up?
なぜそんな話を持ち出す必要があるんだ？
Calm down!
落ち着いて！
Are we working on designing or
我々はデザインに取り組んでいるのか、それとも
carrying boxes?
箱を運ぶ？
So that I can prepare myself.
そうすることで、心の準備ができる。
In the pattern,
このパターンでは
we’re trying to cooperate the contemporary Thai elements
私たちは現代のタイの要素と協力しようとしている。
so, we think of Thai silk.
だから、私たちはタイのシルクを思い浮かべる。
Thai silk is a local wisdom.
タイシルクは地元の知恵なのだ。
I think it is
それは
what we should conserve
守るべきもの
by cooperating Thai silk patterns into this collection of jewelry.
タイシルクのパターンをこのジュエリー・コレクションに取り入れたのだ。
Pim,
ピム
do you think
どう思う？
this collection
このコレクション
looks the same as the last one.
前回と同じように見える。
Exactly,
その通りだ、
except
ただし
P’Prim isn’t the one who came up with this repetitive idea.
この繰り返しのアイデアを思いついたのはP'プリムではない。
Excuse me,
すみません、
what are you guys talking about?
何を言っているんだ？
We are in a meeting room.
私たちは会議室にいる。
Have some manners?
マナーを守れ？
It’s not that
というわけではない。
we weren’t just chatting
ただおしゃべりをしていただけではない
but we
しかし
were discussing about the designs.
デザインについて話し合っていた。
Why don’t you two just stand up and
なぜ二人とも立たないんだ？
discuss it with all of us then.
それなら、私たち全員で話し合おう。
Stand up!
立ち上がれ！
Erm..
あの...
Prim, I think you shouldn’t be upset at them.
プリム、あなたは彼らに腹を立ててはいけないと思う。
I don’t have any problem
何の問題もない
I just want to teach them to
私はただ、彼らに
be opinionated.
意見を言う
You know
ご存知でしょう。
by sharing your opinion
ご意見をお聞かせください
is a key part in developing a product.
は製品開発における重要な部分である。
If you don’t have the guts to do that,
その度胸がないのなら、
how can you present your own designs?
自分のデザインをどのように発表できるか？
What do you say?
なんて言うんだ？
Lin!
リン
I think
私は思う。
even if we still want to keep our brand identity
たとえブランド・アイデンティティを維持したくても
but
しかし
this collection
このコレクション
looks too similar to the one
あまりにも似ている
that came out in the same season last year.
昨年の同シーズンに発売された。
Eh!
え！
What are you talking about?
何を言っているんだ？
You are just an intern.
君はただのインターンだ。
How can you criticize these pieces?
どうしてこれらの作品を批判できるのか？
Erm,
えー、
didn’t you ask for my opinion?
私の意見を聞かなかったのか？
So I just said
だから私はこう言った。
what I saw.
私が見たもの
Do you know
ご存知ですか？
how much profit that collection
そのコレクションがどれだけの利益を生むか
made for our company?
わが社のために？
Are newly grads like you guys can take a risk
君たちのような新卒者はリスクを取れるのか？
if we came out with ne designs
もし我々がネのデザインを出したら
and we can’t keep the loyalty of our customers?
それなのに、顧客の忠誠心を維持できないのだろうか？
If those customers don’t come back
もしその顧客が戻ってこなければ
what would you do?
あなたならどうする？
Can you be responsible for that?
その責任は取れるのか？
Interrns.
中断する。
One month later
1カ月後
What am I doing?
私は何をしているんだ？
Aren’t you tired my boy?
疲れていないかい？
I’m tired to the point that I’m used to it.
慣れている分、疲れているんだ。
The situation isn’t getting better at all
状況はまったく良くなっていない
at you office?
オフィスで？
No, not at all.
いや、全然。
It’s been a month and
もう1カ月になる。
I haven’t got a chance to design something.
何かをデザインする機会がないんだ。
I’m thinking that I made the wrong decision in coming to work here.
ここで働くのは間違った決断だったと思っている。
You’ll be fine.
大丈夫だよ。
You will get through this.
きっと乗り越えられる。
It’s been weeks
ここ数週間
and you haven’t met him in real life.
そして、あなたは彼と実際に会ったことがない。
I’m afraid to do that.
それが怖いんだ。
P’Sun, do you think we will ever have a chance to meet each other just once?
プサン、私たちが一度だけ会う機会があると思う？
Oh wow!
すごい！
I just got back
帰ってきたばかりだ
and my deary little brother
そして愛しい弟よ
just show up right away.
すぐに来てくれ
Of course, I have to come.
もちろん、私は行かなければならない。
It’s been a while I really miss you.
久しぶりだね、本当に会いたいよ。
So how is it?
それでどうなんだ？
Is the company still the same as you told me?
会社はまだ同じですか？
Not a thing has changed.
何も変わっていない。
Our employees still stuck with the old patterns.
従業員はまだ古いパターンにこだわっている。
Nothing’s new.
新しいことは何もない。
Maybe they are afraid of making mistakes.
ミスを恐れているのかもしれない。
So this is the problem that
つまり、これが問題なのだ。
make our sales don’t go higher.
売上が上がらないようにするためだ。
It’s not just that
それだけではない。
I think there’s something else as well.
他にも何かあると思う。
Something else?
他に何か？
If I find anything more
また何か見つけたら
I will tell you right away.
すぐに話すよ。
And now,
そして今、
it’s been a month exactly.
ちょうど1カ月になる。
Your job is over right?
仕事は終わったんだろう？
About the deal that we made,
私たちが交わした契約について、
I’ll get that gone for you.
それは僕がやっておくよ
Hia,
ヒア
can I stay for one or two more months?
あと1、2ヶ月いてもいいですか？
I’ll tell you later.
後で話すよ。
What makes you wanna stay longer?
長く滞在したい理由は？
I remembered when I asked you to work there
あそこで働かないかと誘ったときのことを思い出したよ
you didn't want to do that.
そんなことはしたくなかったはずだ。
What is it?
それは何ですか？
There’s nothing.
何もないよ。
Just leave me alone.
ほっといてくれ。
Are you sure about that?
それは確かですか？
If mom finds out that you’re back and didn't tell her,
もし母さんが、君が戻ってきたことを知ったら、母さんには言わなかった、
you’ll be in trouble.
あなたはトラブルに巻き込まれる
Alright!
わかったよ！
I got it.
私はそれを手に入れた。
How about you?
あなたはどうですか？
Since you are already back here,
もうここに戻っているのだから、
will you go and meet that person?
その人に会いに行きますか？
I think
私は思う。
that I’m going to see him
彼に会いに行く
but I got scare that
しかし、私は怖くなった。
he’s going to be like everyone that I've ever been with.
彼は私がこれまで付き合ってきた人たちと同じになる。
No, I don’t think so
いや、そうは思わない
I’ve got a hunch that
予感がするんだ。
this one will be better than anyone.
これは誰よりも優れているだろう。
What a weird thing to say!
なんて変なことを言うんだ！
Do you know something?
何かご存知ですか？
No,
いや、
nope.
いや。
Not at all.
全然違うよ。
No, for real!
いや、本当だ！
You’re laughing!
笑っているね！
Hia!
ヒア
What do you know?
何を知っている？
I’m just gonna go unload tonight.
今夜は荷物を下ろしに行くだけだ。
If I think of something I will tell you right away.
何か思いついたらすぐに言うよ。
Heyy!
やあ！
Just tell me now/Let me go
教えてくれ
Hia,
ヒア
I’m leaving.
僕は帰るよ。
I want to eat Somtam.
ソムタムを食べたい。
You already ate three dishes. Is it not enough?
もう3皿食べたでしょ。まだ足りない？
How hungry are you?
お腹は空いていますか？
Well,
まあね、
it was super delicious.
超美味しかった。
Ops!
作戦だ！
We’re sorry.
申し訳ない。
What are they doing?
彼らは何をしているんだ？
Yeah!
そうだね！
The atmosphere is
雰囲気は
very serious.
非常に深刻だ。
P’Prim,
プリム
What are you all doing?
皆さんは何をしているのですか？
Is there anything for us to help?
何かお手伝いできることはありますか？
Hahaha!
ハハハ！
You just embarrassed yourself.
恥をかいただけだ。
Watch and learn.
見て学べ。
Hello! P’Juladis.
こんにちは！P'Juladisです。
Why do you have to sneak up on me?
なぜ私に忍び寄る必要があるの？
Er..
えー
Phew!
ふぅ！
what are you doing?
何をしているんだ？
Of course, we’re designing.
もちろん、デザインはしている。
Our whole department have to
私たちの部署全体が
find the best idea
最高のアイデアを見つける
and compete with other design departments.
そして他のデザイン部門と競争する。
It counts as an annual evaluation
年次評価としてカウントされる
and also an opportunity to shine.
そして輝く機会でもある。
Can we interns compete too?
私たちインターンも出場できますか？
Hahaha
ハハハ
What?
え？
What did you just say?
今何と言った？
Well,
まあね、
can we join the competition?
コンペに参加できる？
Ahh
ああ
If all of you
もし皆さんが
You
あなた
and you
そして
are confident
自信がある
that you are better than us
あなたは私たちよりも優れている
then try.
それなら、やってみよう。
Please do your best.
頑張ってください。
This is it.
これだ。
Our opportunity are
我々のチャンスは
finally here.
ようやくここまで来た。
Fighting!
戦っている！
Good morning, everyone.
皆さん、おはようございます。
I hope that you are all doing well.
皆さんが元気でいることを願っています。
After our last meeting
前回のミーティング後
had me thought
と思った。
about back
背中について
when our Soul High Jewelry
ソウル・ハイ・ジュエリー
were glorious.
は輝いていた。
But today
しかし今日
it’s not the same anymore.
もう同じじゃない。
We really need to change.
私たちは本当に変わらなければならない。
I would like to thank everyone
皆さんに感謝したい。
for helping
を助けるために
our company
当社
moving forward.
前進する
I also would like everyone
また、私は皆さんに
to cooperate
協力する
with
と
our new president.
私たちの新大統領だ。
Which is
どちらが
Mr. Suriyen Thanahirankan.
スリエン・タナヒランカン氏
My own son.
自分の息子だ。
What?
え？
Has Mr.Sun returned from abroad?
孫さんは海外から戻られたのですか？
Gossip Time
ゴシップ・タイム
What do you think is
どう思う？
the reason why Madame Wang stepped down from her company?
マダム・ワンが会社を辞めた理由は？
I don’t know.
分からないよ。
Maybe she’s just tired.
疲れているのかもしれない。
I’m not sure too
私もよくわからない
but it might be good.
でも、いいかもしれない。
I heard that her son would take over this company.
彼女の息子がこの会社を継ぐと聞いた。
What do you think a son of that auntie
あのおばちゃんの息子をどう思う？
would be like?
のようなものだろうか？
I think
私は思う。
her son
息子
may be full of egos just like her.
彼女もまた、エゴの塊なのかもしれない。
He’s not.
彼は違う。
He may not be
彼はそうではないかもしれない。
egotistic.
エゴイスティックだ。
Why?
なぜですか？
Do you know her son?
息子さんをご存知ですか？
No,
いや、
I just heard from
私はちょうど聞いたところだ。
someone in our team said that
チームの誰かがこう言った。
her son graduated
彼女の息子は卒業した。
from abroad and
海外から、そして
worked there.
そこで働いていた。
Wow!
ワオ！
What a nice profile!
なんて素敵なプロフィールなんだ！
Calm down!
落ち着いて！
You already got a husband.
あなたにはもう夫がいる。
Yo!
ヨー！
Why would you say that?
どうしてそんなことを言うんですか？
People might misunderstand me.
誤解されるかもしれない。
Be quiet!
静かにしなさい！
Don’t you konw?
知らないの？
No wedding means no boyfriend.
結婚式がないということは、ボーイフレンドもいないということだ。
Lin, are you free this Saturday at 7 P.M.?
リン、今週の土曜日の午後7時、空いてる？
Lin,
リン
are you alright?
大丈夫か？
Look
見る
What?!
何だと？
He asked you to a hotel.
彼はあなたをホテルに誘った。
What have you two been talking about? Hotel on a first date.
二人で何を話していたの？初デートのホテルについて。
He might just take me to have dinner.
夕食に連れて行ってくれるかもしれない。
Don’t pessimistic.
悲観的になるな。
No one wants your opinion.
誰もあなたの意見など求めていない。
I’m just talking to myself
独り言だよ
not to you.
あなたには関係ない。
Lin,
リン
what are you going to do?
どうするつもりだ？
Will you go?
行ってくれる？
I
I
don’t know.
わからない。
Actually,
実はね、
this Saturday
今週土曜日
don’t we have to rush our jewelry design?
ジュエリーのデザインを急ぐ必要はないのでは？
You’re right!
その通りだ！
Don’t worry!
心配しないで！
For a date
デートの場合
we will take care of the work for you.
私たちにお任せください。
We will finish it for you.
私たちが仕上げます。
We? What is we?
私たち？私たちとは？
You do that alone.
一人でやるんだ。
If we work
もし我々が働けば
we have to work together.
私たちは協力しなければならない。
It’s due this saturday.
今週の土曜日が期限だ。
Yo, don’t you see? Lin wants to go and
ヨ、わからないのか？林が行きたいのは
opportunities like this don't come very often.
こんなチャンスは滅多にない。
How’s going?
調子はどうだい？
I think
私は思う。
I’m nearly done.
もうすぐ終わるよ。
What do you think
どう思う？
about right here?
この辺りかな？
I think it looks good
いい感じだと思う
but
しかし
you could make it a bit thinner.
もう少し薄くしてもいいかもしれない。
Shit!
クソッ！
It’s 7 P.M.
午後7時だ。
7 P.M.
午後7時
I’ll take care of your outfits.
君の衣装は僕が用意するよ。
Make me look good!
私をよく見せてくれ！
Alright!
わかったよ！
Yo
ヨー
Okay! Okay! Wait! Wait!
オーケーよし待って！
Almost done.
もう少しだ。
Hurry!
急げ！
Turn it off for me.
私のために消してくれ。
Okay
オーケー
Wow!
ワオ！
You look good.
元気そうだね。
Very stunning!
とても見事だ！
Really?
本当に？
Yes.
そうだ。
Wow,
ワオ、
look at how shine and sparkling he is
彼の輝きを見よ
you can be seen from outer space.
宇宙からも見える。
Am I really looking good?
私は本当にいい顔をしているだろうか？
100 out of 100
100点満点中100点
I’ll give you a million.
100万ドルあげるよ。
Don’t you think
そう思わないか？
that it is a little much?
ちょっとやりすぎですか？
More is less!
多かれ少なかれ！
Hey!
やあ！
who’s texting you?
誰からメール？
Ready to see me?
私に会う準備はできた？
Nu-Lin.
ヌーリン
I’m ready.
準備はできている。
I’m counting to see you.
会えてよかった。
Whatever your decision may be
どのような決断であれ
we are here.
私たちはここにいる。
Even though I really don’t want you to go.
本当は行ってほしくないのに。
Let the world see
世界に知らしめる
how stunning you are.
なんて見事なんだ。
Thanks you!
ありがとう！
Feel better?
気分は良くなったか？
So much better.
ずっといい。
Excuse me,
すみません、
err
誤る
I’m a guest of Mr. Sun.
私は孫さんのゲストだ。
He told me that he already made a table reservation.
彼はすでにテーブルを予約していると言った。
Just a moment please.
ちょっと待ってください。
Here you are.
お待たせしました。
He asked me to tell you that
彼は私にこう言った
you can wait in the room
お部屋でお待ちください
which we prepared.
私たちが用意したものだ。
A room?
部屋？
Yes, sir.
はい
P’Sun
プサン
We finally met,
やっと会えた、
Nu-Lin
ニューリン
P’Sun
プサン
Ready to meet each other,
お互いに会う準備はできている、
Nu-Lin?
ヌーリン？
I’m ready.
準備はできている。
Nu-Lin, are you ready to meet up?
ヌーリン、会う準備はできているかい？
Lin,
リン
what are you thinking?
何を考えているんだ？
Hm,
ふむ、
we’ll get to see each other soon.
もうすぐ会えるよ。
Nu-Lin
ニューリン
P’Sun
プサン
Have you been waiting for a long time,
長い間待っていたのですか？
Nu-Lin?
ヌーリン？
Let me take you to your condo.
コンドミニアムに案内しよう。
Didn’t you tell me that you are just an ordinary office worker?
あなたは普通のサラリーマンだと言わなかった？
But,
でもね、
why do you have a motorbike that costs a million baht?
なぜ100万バーツもするバイクを持っているのですか？
We really did nothing
私たちは本当に何もしなかった
just held hands.
ただ手をつないだだけだ。
Are you telling the truth?
本当のことを言っているのか？
The interns that you want to meet are here.
あなたが会いたいインターンはここにいる。
Can I talk with Mr.Salin privately?
サリン氏と個人的に話すことはできますか？
Is there anything that I can do for you sir?
私に何かできることはありますか？
Lin, please give me a chance.
リン、チャンスをくれ。